{"0":{"question_text":"Place Iterative Development Process phases in the correct order.","question_code":"............","option":["inception","elaboration","construction","transition"],"answer":"0,1,2,3"},"1":{"question_text":"Complete the sentence.","question_code":"During the     ...     phase, you work out the business case for the project - roughly how much it will cost and how much it will bring in. You will also need to get a sense of the project's scope. You may need to do some initial analysis to get a sense of the size of the project.","option":["inception","elaboration","construction","transition"],"answer":"0"},"2":{"question_text":"Complete the sentence.","question_code":"You identify project's risks during the ...     phase.","option":["inception","elaboration","construction","transition"],"answer":"1"},"3":{"question_text":"Complete the sentence.","question_code":"...           builds the system in a series of iterations. Each iteration is a mini-project.You do analysis, design, coding, testing, and integration for the use cases assigned to each iteration. ","option":["Inception","Elaboration","Construction","Transition"],"answer":"2"},"4":{"question_text":"Complete the sentence.","question_code":"Code optimization should be done during the     ...      phase.","option":["inception","elaboration","construction","transition"],"answer":"3"},"5":{"question_text":"Complete the sentence.","question_code":"A     ...     is a sequence of steps describing an interaction between a user and a system. ","option":["scenario","use case","goal"],"answer":"0"},"6":{"question_text":"What is the true statement about Use Cases?","question_code":"","option":["A Use Case is a set of scenarios tied together by a common user goal","A Use Case is a main successful scenario without alternative scenarios","A Use Case is a set of scenarios tied together by a packages diagram"],"answer":"0"},"7":{"question_text":"What are the true statements about Use Case actors?","question_code":"","option":["An actor is a role that a user plays with respect to the system","An actor must be a human","An actor can be an external system","An actor can perform only a single Use Case"],"answer":"0,2"},"8":{"question_text":"Complete the sentence.","question_code":"The     ...     relationship occurs when you have a chunk of behavior that is similar across more than one Use Case and you don't want to keep copying the description of that behavior.","option":["include","extend","generalization"],"answer":"0"},"9":{"question_text":"What is the correct statement?","question_code":"A(n)     ...     Diagram describes the typesof objects in the system and the various kinds of static relationships that exist among them.","option":["Class","Interaction","State","Activity"],"answer":"0"},"10":{"question_text":"What is the correct statement?","question_code":"The     ...     perspective has a diagramthat represents the ideas in the domain under study. There is often no direct mapping between ideas and software classes - it can be considered language-independent.","option":["conceptual","specification","implementation","testing"],"answer":"0"},"11":{"question_text":"What are the true statments about Class Diagram associations?","question_code":"","option":["Associations represent relationships between instances of classes","Associations are the processes that a class knows to carry out","Associations can be unidirectional","Associations can be bidirectional"],"answer":"0,2,3"},"12":{"question_text":"What is the 'optionText' on the Class Diagram?","question_code":"","option":["attribute","association","role","assertion","modifier"],"answer":"0"},"13":{"question_text":"The full UML syntax for operations is:","question_code":"...         ...        ...       :      ...       ...","option":["visibility","name","(parameter-list)","return-type","{property}"],"answer":"0,1,2,3,4"},"14":{"question_text":"Attributes and operations modifiers are:","question_code":"...  (public)...  (protected)...  (private)","option":["+","#","-","~","$","*","!"],"answer":"0,1,2"},"15":{"question_text":"What relationship does the Class Diagram show?","question_code":"","option":["attribute","association","role","assertion","generalization"],"answer":"4"},"16":{"question_text":"Option's name should not be 'null'.What Class Diagram shows the constraint?","question_code":"","option":["diagram A","diagram B","diagram C"],"answer":"0"},"17":{"question_text":"What are the true statments about Interaction Diagrams?","question_code":"","option":["Interaction Diagrams describe behavior of several objects","Interaction Diagrams describe behaviour of a single object","An Interaction Diagram captures the behavior of a single Use Case","An Interaction Diagram captures the behavior of many Use Cases"],"answer":"0,2"},"18":{"question_text":"Within a sequence diagram:","question_code":"--------->   represents ...[some_text]  represents ...     *       represents ...     X       represents ...","option":["message","condition","iteration","deletion","return","self-call","creation","object"],"answer":"0,1,2,3"},"19":{"question_text":"What are the true statments about asynchronous messageson Sequence Diagrams?","question_code":"","option":["Asynchronous messages can create a new thread.","Asynchronous messages can not create a new thread.","Asynchronous messages can create a new object.","Asynchronous messages can not create a new object.","Asynchronous messages can communicate with other threads.","Asynchronous messages can not communicate with other threads."],"answer":"0,2,4"},"20":{"question_text":"Use CRC cards for:","question_code":"","option":["generating long lists of low-level responsibilities of classes.","explore an interaction between classes.","summarizing the key responsibilities of classes","finding attributes and methods of classes"],"answer":"1,2"},"21":{"question_text":"Finish the correct statement.","question_code":"Class scope features are    ...   on a class diagram","option":["underlined","uppercased","lowercased","italicized"],"answer":"0"},"22":{"question_text":"How can you show that any instance of the superclass must be an instance of one of the subtypes of a group?","question_code":"","option":["{complete}","[complete]","<<complete>>","(complete)"],"answer":"0"},"23":{"question_text":"How can you show that objects are allowed to change type within the subtyping structure?","question_code":"","option":["{dynamic}","[dynamic]","<<dynamic>>","(dynamic)"],"answer":"2"},"24":{"question_text":"Finish the correct statement.","question_code":"With       ...      , the part object may belong to only one whole. The parts are usually expected to live and die with the whole.","option":["aggregation","composition","classification","generalization"],"answer":"1"},"25":{"question_text":"What are true statements about derived attributes on Implementation Class Diagrams?","question_code":"","option":["They can be calculated from other attributes.","They can not be calculated from other attributes. ","They are valuable for annotating fields that are used as caches for performance reasons.","They indicate that the value of that attribute may not change during the lifetime of the source object."],"answer":"0,2"},"26":{"question_text":"What is true about Value Objects?","question_code":"","option":["Value Objects should be immutable.","Value Objects should be mutable.","Many interchangeable copies of Value Object may exist.","Copies may be disallowed for Value Objects.","Value Objects are compared by identities.","Value Objects are compared by values they represent."],"answer":"0,2,5"},"27":{"question_text":"What does the {frozen} constraint on the attribute mean?","question_code":"","option":["It indicates that the value of that attribute may not change during the lifetime of the source object. ","It indicates that the attribute is a read-only."],"answer":"0"},"28":{"question_text":"What is true about Qualified Associations on Class Diagrams?","question_code":"","option":["Qualified Associations provide approximately the same functionality as indexes.","Typically the Qualifier is an attribute of the class on the opposite end of the association.","Qualified Associations simplify the navigation across complex associations by providing keys to narrow the selection of objects.","Qualified Associations define the number of objects that may participate in relationship.","Qualified Associations define the rules that must be enforced to ensure the integrity of the relationship."],"answer":"0,1,2"},"29":{"question_text":"What is true about Association Classes on Class Diagrams?","question_code":"","option":["They allow designer to add attributes, operations, and other features to associations.","An Association Class encapsulates information about an association.","An Association Class is attached to the association with a dashed line.","An Association Class is attached to the association with a solid line.","An Association Class is attached to the association with a dotted line.","An Association Class contains the rules that must be enforced to ensure the integrity of the relationship."],"answer":"0,1,2"},"30":{"question_text":"Finish the correct statements about visibility","question_code":"A     ...    member is visible anywhere in the program and may be called by any object within the system.A     ...    member may be used only by the class that defines it.A     ...    member may be used only by:a) the class that defines it b) a subclass of that class.","option":["public","private","protected","package"],"answer":"0,1,2"},"31":{"question_text":"What is true about Packages?","question_code":"","option":["Packages dependencies are transitive.","Packages dependencies are not transitive.","Packages offer answers about how to reduce dependencies in your system.","Packages  help to see what the dependencies are."],"answer":"1,3"},"32":{"question_text":"What is true about State Diagrams?","question_code":"","option":["They describe all of the possible states that a particular object can get into and  how the object's state changes as a result of events that reach the object.","They describe the behavior of several objects within a single Use Case.","They describe the types of objects in the system and the various kinds of relationships that exist among them.","They show the various components in a system and their dependencies."],"answer":"0"},"33":{"question_text":"What is the syntax for a transition label in State Diagram?","question_code":"...       [    ...    ] \/     ...","option":["Event","Guard","Action","Activity"],"answer":"0,1,2"},"34":{"question_text":"Complete the following sentences about State Diagrams artifacts.","question_code":"A(n)    ...    is associated with a transition and is considered to be a process that occures quickly and is not interruptible.A(n)    ...    is associated with a state and can take longer. It may be interrupted by some event.A(n)    ...    is a logical condition that will return only \"true\" or \"false\".","option":["Action","Activity","Guard","Event"],"answer":"0,1,2"},"35":{"question_text":"What is true about State Diagrams?","question_code":"","option":["State Diagrams are good at describing the behavior of an object across several Use Cases. ","State Diagrams are good at describing the behavior of several objects across several Use Cases.","State Diagrams are good at describing the behavior of several objects in a single Use Case.","State Diagrams are good at showing the general sequence of actions for several objects and Use Cases."],"answer":"0"},"36":{"question_text":"What does the ' * ' marker indicate?","question_code":"","option":["It shows iterations without having to construct a loop.","It indicates that the activity is executed many times.","It shows that several activities need to be executed together in some manner.","It shows a fork."],"answer":"0,1"},"37":{"question_text":"Use Activity Diagrams in the following situations:","question_code":"","option":["Analyzing a use case.   ","Describing a complicated sequential algorithm.   ","Understanding workflow.   ","Trying to see how objects collaborate.","Trying to see how an object behaves over its lifetime.   ","Representing complex conditional logic."],"answer":"0,1,2"},"38":{"question_text":"You need to show the physical relationships among software and hardware components in the delivered system. What kind of diagram can you use for that?","question_code":"","option":["Deployment Diagram","Activity Diagram","Class Diagram","State Diagram"],"answer":"0"},"39":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of an Activity Diagram?","question_code":"","option":["Shows behavior with control structure. Can show many objects over many uses, many objects in single use case, or implementation of method.","Shows static structure of concepts, types, and classes.","Helps get to essence of class's purpose. Good for exploring how to implement use case.","Shows physical layout of components on hardware nodes."],"answer":"0"},"40":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of a Class Diagram?","question_code":"","option":["Shows behavior with control structure. Can show many objects over many uses, many objects in single use case, or implementation of method.","Shows static structure of concepts, types, and classes.","Helps get to essence of class's purpose. Good for exploring how to implement use case.","Shows physical layout of components on hardware nodes."],"answer":"1"},"41":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of CRC Cards?","question_code":"","option":["Shows behavior with control structure. Can show many objects over many uses, many objects in single use case, or implementation of method.","Shows static structure of concepts, types, and classes.","Helps get to essence of class's purpose. Good for exploring how to implement use case.","Shows physical layout of components on hardware nodes."],"answer":"2"},"42":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of a Deployment Diagram?","question_code":"","option":["Shows behavior with control structure. Can show many objects over many uses, many objects in single use case, or implementation of method.","Shows static structure of concepts, types, and classes.","Helps get to essence of class's purpose. Good for exploring how to implement use case.","Shows physical layout of components on hardware nodes."],"answer":"3"},"43":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of a \"Design by Contract\" technique?","question_code":"","option":["Provides rigorous definition of operation's purpose and class's legal state.","Shows how several objects collaborate in single Use Case.","Shows groups of classes and dependencies among them.","Offers useful bits of analysis, design, and coding techniques. "],"answer":"0"},"44":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of an Interaction Diagram?","question_code":"","option":["Provides rigorous definition of operation's purpose and class's legal state.","Shows how several objects collaborate in single Use Case.","Shows groups of classes and dependencies among them.","Offers useful bits of analysis, design, and coding techniques. "],"answer":"1"},"45":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of a Package Diagram?","question_code":"","option":["Provides rigorous definition of operation's purpose and class's legal state.","Shows how several objects collaborate in single Use Case.","Shows groups of classes and dependencies among them.","Offers useful bits of analysis, design, and coding techniques. "],"answer":"2"},"46":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of Patterns?","question_code":"","option":["Provides rigorous definition of operation's purpose and class's legal state.","Shows how several objects collaborate in single Use Case.","Shows groups of classes and dependencies among them.","Offers useful bits of analysis, design, and coding techniques. "],"answer":"3"},"47":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of Refactoring?","question_code":"","option":["Helps in making changes to working program to improve structure.","Basis for system testing.","Offers useful bits of analysis, design, and coding techniques.","Helps get to essence of class's purpose."],"answer":"0"},"48":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of a State Diagram?","question_code":"","option":["Shows how single object behaves across many Use Cases.","Shows how many objects behave in single Use Case.","Shows static structure of concepts, types, and classes. ","Helps get to essence of class's purpose."],"answer":"0"},"49":{"question_text":"What is the purpose of a Use Case?","question_code":"","option":["Elicits requirements from users in meaningful chunks. ","Offers useful bits of analysis, design, and coding techniques.","Is a basis for system testing.","Provides rigorous definition of operation's purpose and class's legal state. ","Provides class debugging enhancements."],"answer":"0,2"}}